xxxchurch.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy And Rights Of Use - XXXchurch.com

## Thanks, you're signed up!

Thanks for registering for the 30 Day Challenge!

We will be sending you an email shortly.

_Please make sure you do these two things so you get your emails:  
_  
**1\. Add craig@xxxchurch.com to your address book  
2\. Mark your email from us as NOT SPAM  
**

__PS.  If you don't get your email in the next few hours check your spam folder.  
____Find out how you can make sure our emails get to your inbox  _[ ** _here_**](https://www.xxxchurch.com/make-sure-get-emails) ** _._**_ ×

## RIGHTS OF USE

Per our Creative Commons Attribution-NoDerivatives 4.0 International License you are free to:

 _Share_ — copy and redistribute the materials on this site in any medium or format for any purpose, even commercially.  
The licensor cannot revoke these freedoms as long as you follow the license terms.

 **Under the following Terms:**

 _Attribution_ — You must give appropriate credit, provide a link to the license, and indicate if changes were made. You may do so in any reasonable manner, but not in any way that suggests the licensor endorses you or your use.

 _NoDerivatives_ — If you remix, transform, or build upon the material, you may not distribute the modified material.

 _No additional restrictions_ — You may not apply legal terms or technological measures that legally restrict others from doing anything the license permits.

 **Notices:**

You do not have to comply with the license for elements of the material in the public domain or where your use is permitted by an applicable exception or limitation.

No warranties are given. The license may not give you all of the permissions necessary for your intended use. For example, other rights such as publicity, privacy, or moral rights may limit how you use the material.

This is a human-readable summary of (and not a substitute for) the [creative commons license](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/4.0/legalcode "Creative Commons License").

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

 **What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

 **When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

 **How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.  
• To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

 **How do we protect visitor information?**

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards as we do not process financial transactions on this site.  
We use regular Malware Scanning.

 **Do we use ‘cookies’?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

 **We use cookies to:**  
Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you disable cookies off, it won’t affect the users experience.

 **Third Party Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include third party links on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Opting out:**  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act**

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. – See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

 **According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:**  
Users can visit our site anonymously  
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.  
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’, and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:  
• On our Privacy Policy Page

 **COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

 **CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

 _We collect your email address in order to:_  
• Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions  
• Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders  
• We may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service  
• Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred

 _To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:_  
• NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses  
• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way  
• Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters  
• Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.  
• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly  
• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

XXXchurch.com is a ministry of [Fireproof Ministries, Inc. a registered 501c3](http://fireproofministries.com/#features)

 **Contacting Us  
**If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us [here](https://www.xxxchurch.com/contact "Contact").

## Thanks, you're signed up!

We will be sending your first email shortly.

_Please make sure you do these two things so you get your emails:_

**1\. Add craig@xxxchurch.com to your address book  
2\. Mark your 1st email from us as NOT SPAM**

__PS.  If you don't get your 1st email in the next 5 minutes check your spam folder.__  
__Find out how you can make sure our emails get to your inbox  _[ ** _here_**](https://www.xxxchurch.com/make-sure-get-emails) ** _._**_ ×

## Thanks, you're signed up!

Thanks for registering for the 30 Day Challenge!

We will be sending you an email shortly.

_Please make sure you do these two things so you get your emails:  
_  
**1\. Add craig@xxxchurch.com to your address book  
2\. Mark your email from us as NOT SPAM  
**

__PS.  If you don't get your email in the next few hours check your spam folder.  
____Find out how you can make sure our emails get to your inbox  _[ ** _here_**](https://www.xxxchurch.com/make-sure-get-emails) ** _._**_ ×
